oh no no no no no no no no yeah we're good October 18th and October 18th okay
I don't know I have October 8th everybody have October 18th I have August 2nd
I got August 2nd I got August 18th I got one of each you got SUA for the 18th and council for the second
how did it do that some of one and some of another well I printed mine off and I printed
mine okay we're gonna we're gonna go ahead and it's not gonna help this is the SCA right yep
we're gonna go ahead and start the SCA you want one of these so now I'll be in the
dark
yeah all the council's are on okay everybody all right I thought we recognized Scott for 15
years it's on the council or SUA it's on the council he'll have to wait a few minutes the SUA won't tell Calvin we're gonna
call to order this regular meeting of the MIAMI
and Special Utility Authority for today's date and time.
Item number two on the agenda is an indication by the pastor of Activated Church, David Jackson.
David, thanks for being here.
Let's have a word of prayer.
Father God, we come before you as people who trust in you.
We believe in you.
We believe in your word.
We believe that you are wisdom, Lord.
Father, I pray that you bless these men and women before us, guide them in their leadership.
May they be agreeable.
May they be decisive.
May they stand together in unity, Lord.
And may you give them wisdom to guide us not only in the present, but into the future, Lord.
Forgive us where we fail.
Forgive us where we stumble, Lord.
And may you be glorified through it all.
In the name of Jesus Christ, amen.
Amen.
Thank you, God.
It's your big place, God.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America
and to the republic for which it stands,
one nation,
under God,
indivisible,
with liberty and justice for all.
Thank you.
Item four is public input and unscheduled personal appearances.
Is there any audience that wishes to address the authority on any of the agenda items?
If there are none, item five is consent agenda.
Staff is recommending items six through eight, the consent agenda.
If there are no questions, I'd entertain a motion.
I make a motion to approve item six through eight in the consent agenda.
And a second?
Second.
Roll call, please.
Johnson?
Aye.
Weston?
Lewis?
Aye.
Schultz?
New business?
Any new business, Kim?
You sitting in for Dean, I see.
No.
Staff reports, they're in your packet.
Staff is available if there are any questions.
If there are none.
Trustee community announcements, anything to announce?
No.
Item 12 is adjournment.
Do you make a motion to adjourn?
Yes, I do.
I second that.
Roll call, please.
Johnson?
Aye.
Schultz?
Weston?
Aye.
Lewis?
Okay, we are now going to...